<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Water Journal</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to the Water journal app setup!</string>
    <string name="announce_weight">Your weight:</string>
    <string name="announce_target">Your daily water target:</string>
    <string name="placeholder_x">x</string>
    <string name="insert_weight">Insert your weight:</string>
    <string name="kg">kg</string>
    <string name="announce_water_target">Your calculated daily water target:</string>
    <string name="announce_info">You can set a custom water target in the app preferences.</string>
    <string name="whenReady">When ready:</string>
    <string name="toMainButton">Continue</string>
    <string name="text_app_name">Water Journal</string>
    <string name="button_store_user_data">Save</string>
    <string name="button_add_drink">Add</string>
    <string name="text_preferences">App preferences:</string>
    <string name="button_drinking_history">History</string>
    <string name="button_home">Home</string>
    <string name="button_save_preferences">Save</string>
    <string name="button_tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="text_add_weight">Insert weight (kg)</string>
    <string name="text_drink_ml">ml</string>
    <string name="button_remove_resent">Remove recent</string>
    <string name="text_sex">Sex</string>
    <string name="text_weight">Weight:</string>
    <string name="button_preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="text_add_drink">Add drink:</string>
    <string name="text_daily_goal">Daily water goal status:</string>
    <string name="text_daily_goal_pref">Daily goal:</string>
    <string name="text_amount_goal">Amount / Goal</string>
    <string name="text_history">Your drinking history:</string>
    <string name="title_home">Water Journal</string>
    <string name="title_history">History</string>
    <string name="title_prefenrences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="waterdrop">waterdrop</string>
    <string name="text_kg_pref">kg</string>
    <string name="text_l_pref">litres</string>
    <string name="title_tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="text_tips_water">Water \n \nMaintenance fluid balance \nRegulates body temperature \nSupports digestion \nTransport and absorb nutrients \nRemoves metabolic products \n(thl)</string>
    <string name="text_tips_child">For children \n \nNormally, a child needs 1 to 1.5 liters of fluid a day. \nIn cold weather, the need for fluid may be even higher. \nProvide your child to drink evenly throughout the day. \nThe child has drunk too little if he pees less often than usual and the pee is darker than usual. \nDehydration can also cause headaches and irritability. \n(thl)</string>
    <string name="text_tips_adult">For adults \n\nDrink 2-3 liters of fluid a day. \nAbout half of this should be drunk and the other half with food. \nSweating and saunaing increase the need for fluid. \nIf you drink coffee or alcohol, always drink a glass of water with it. \n(thl)</string>
    <string name="text_tips_pregnant">For pregnant women  \n\nRemember to drink enough.  \nYour body produces extra blood and needs fluid.  \nThe fluid also supports metabolism, reduces swelling and prevents constipation.  \nIt is good to drink skimmed milk products 5-6 dl a day.  \nThis will give you enough calcium and vitamin D.  \nDo not drink alcohol.  \nAlcohol can harm the fetus at any stage of pregnancy.  \n(thl)</string>
    <string name="text_tips_breastfeeding">For breastfeeding \n\nWhen you breastfeed, you lose fluid. \nSo drink about the amount of breast milk. \nHowever, extra drinking does not increase the amount of breast milk. Do not drink too much fluid. \nMore than five liters a day is already clearly too much for the body. \nSuitable drinks include water, skim milk and buttermilk, tea and low-sugar, dilute juices. \nEnjoy your coffee in moderation. \nExcessive coffee drinking can make a baby restless, as some of the caffeine passes into breast milk. \nAvoid alcohol while breastfeeding. \nAlcohol is eliminated from breast milk as quickly as from the blood. \nThe highest alcohol content is about 30-60 minutes after drinking alcohol. \n(thl)</string>
    <string name="text_tips_elderly">For the elderly \n\nDrink 1 to 1.5 liters a day. \nDrink even if you are not thirsty. \nIn addition to water and dairy products, good drinks include whole juices, juice drinks and soft drinks. \nEat liquid foods such as salads and cold soups. \nReserve a daily drink in the fridge in the fridge. \nThis will also allow you to monitor how much you drink. \nDrink more fluids in the morning and during the day. \nDrinking plenty in the evening increases urine output at night. \nDehydration is especially severe in the elderly, as there is less water in the body than in the younger ones. \nDehydration can occur very quickly. \nIt can lead to, among other things, a drop in blood pressure and falls. \nSome medications also increase the need for fluid. \n(thl)</string>
</resources>